# Alexey Gladkov

Student

Email: adamsonbor@mail.ru
Address: Yerevan, Arshakunyats 25
Phone: +37441130499
Date of birth: Apr 13, 1999
Nationality: Russian
Link: https://github.com/Adamsonbor



### **OBJECTIVE**

Hi, i am Alexey. I have a great motivation to learn and improve my skills. I recently moved to Yerevan and am ready to work.

Always looking to learn new skills, take on extra responsibilities, and grow professionally.

For more than 2 years I have been educating myself every day. I am ready to show my skills at work.

You can see my GitHub!

https://github.com/Adamsonbor

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Russia, Surgut

Mar 2020 - Dec 2021

Russia, Surgut Jan 2022 - Aug 2022 Oil and gas production operator

Surgutneftegaz

Control of oil and gas production. Repair and maintenance of oil and gas equipment

# **Assistant Manager**

Leroy Merlin

Communication with customers. Organization and planing of working day. Assistance in the selection of building materials.

#### **EDUCATION**

Russia, Surgut Sep 2014 - Jun 2019

Armenia, Yerevan Nov 2022 - Present

## Development and operation of oil and gas fields Surgut Oil College

# **Artificial Intelligence**

42 Yerevan

An initiative of the EU-supported TUMO Labs, the educational program within the EU TUMO Convergence Center for Engineering and Applied Science, 42 Yerevan joins a network of France-based programming schools, with locations in Tokyo, Amsterdam, Rio de Janeiro, Moscow, and 26 other cities around the world.

### **SKILLS**

- Python
- Pandas
- Numpy
- Matplotlib
- · Scikit learn
- Asyncio
- SQL
- Teamwork
- Communication skills
- Stress resistance

### LANGUAGES

Russian Native

English

Intermediate